http://www.aifia.org/pg/privacy_policy.php

Search this site
Home Partners Initiatives Education Research News About AIfIA
Privacy Policy
The Asilomar Institute for Information Architecture ("the Institute") believes in protecting personal information whenever necessary. The Institute also aims to connect our network of people together for the benefit of all and strives to do so while respecting personal privacy and confidential information.
The Institute collects personally identifiable information for a number of reasons, including but not limited to membership, volunteer recruitment, and general correspondence. When this voluntary information is provided, it should be assumed that:
Membership information may be shared with other members
Volunteer information may be shared with other volunteers
All information may be reviewed by the Institute's Board of Directors and Leadership Council
Participation in surveys is voluntary, and the information received will not be shared in any way that could identify the participants.
The Institute does not sell or share personally identifiable information in any way that is not covered in this policy. If there is a change to this policy that will affect how we handle personal information, the affected individuals will be notified via email.
“Poor or missing information architecture neuters content, design, and programming and devalues the site for its owners as well as the audience it was created to serve.”—Jeffrey Zeldman
Contact Us About this Site Privacy Policy Hosting by DreamHost © 2005 AIfIA
